DIGIORGIO BENJAMIN

PROFILE INFO

With a love for travel and people I can fit into any team and thrive working with others or alone. I have a deep interest in law, marketing, programming and data analysis, and love when they overlap.

Having worked in many fast paced environments and have honed my time-management skills.

CONTACT INFO



Github

https://github.com/bendigiorgio



Email

bendigiorgio@gmail.com



LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/bendigiorgio

MY SKILLS

Python

Excel

SQL

Next.js

React

Tableau

Japanese

WORK EXPERIENCE

Optical Assembler Darkly Labs (Melbourne)

2017-201

- Parts/Machine Assembly
- Accounting

Floor Staff WEGO (Japan) 2019-2021

Head Chef

2020-2022

Italian Basil (Japan)

- · Head of stock management/ordering
- New menu development
- Management of POS, delivery systems, shop inventory (Separate from restaurant)

Hall Staff

2022-Present

Hotel Nikko Fukuoka (Japan)

EDUCATION HISTORY

Bachelor of Commerce

2019-2023

Deakin University

· Major in Marketing

Overseas Study

2019 - 2019

Essca School of Management

 Risk Management, Luxury Brand Management

CERTIFICATIONS

Google Data Analytics
Professional

JLPT Japanese

Language Proficiency

CHECK OUT MORE

